{
    "subject": "resource/Chennakeshava_Temple,_Aralaguppe",
    "predicate": "ontology/isPartOf",
    "object": "resource/Karnataka",
    "human_readable": "The Chennakeshava Temple, Aralaguppe is part of Karnataka.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9765129089355469,
            "question": "Is the Chennakeshava Temple part of Karnataka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7698498964309692,
            "question": "Where is the Chennakeshava Temple located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7687644958496094,
            "question": "What is the name of the temple in Aralaguppe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6253313422203064,
            "question": "Which Indian state houses the Chennakeshava Temple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6046046018600464,
            "question": "To which region of India does Aralaguppe belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5518767237663269,
            "question": "What state in India does the Chennakeshava Temple belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4978567957878113,
            "question": "The Chennakeshava Temple is known for its architectural style. What type of architecture is it?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48406732082366943,
            "question": "Aralaguppe is part of which administrative division?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2484239786863327,
            "question": "What is the name of the village where the temple is situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.181197851896286,
            "question": "Besides religious significance, what else might the temple contribute to the local area?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Chennakeshava Temple, Aralaguppe is part of Karnataka.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2356_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the village where the temple is situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2356_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Aralaguppe is part of which administrative division?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2356_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Chennakeshava Temple is known for its architectural style. What type of architecture is it?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2356_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2356_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response in the requested JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in all the documents supports this triple. Each document mentions that the Chennakeshava temple is located in Aralaguppe, which is described as a small town in the Tumkur district of Karnataka state, India."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents confirms that the Chennakeshava Temple is located in Aralaguppe, which is a town in Karnataka. Therefore, the statement \"The Chennakeshava Temple, Aralaguppe is part of Karnataka\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}